onlinechat.co.in 2015-12-07

# PrivacyPolicy | Online Chat

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices of onlinechat.co.in We have provided this statement for your personal information and safety.

Information is collected from users at several different points on our website, detailed in this statement.

We will not collect or share any information on our site in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

Registration: Registration is an optional service and users are not required to register. During registration a user is required to give a verifiable email address. This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site.

Site and Service Updates: From time to time we may send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email.

Cookies: A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. By setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site.

Links: This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that OnlineChat is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by OnlineChat.

Log Files: We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ moonlinechatvement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Notification of Changes: If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
